Guide to the Alvin P. Shapiro Papers, 1942-1998 UA.90.F64
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Personal Papers, 1942-1998; VI.
  - Correspondence, 1953-1981; 1974-1979; 2. (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
    This subseries includes personal and professional correspondence from Shapiro's time as associate dean for Academic Affairs (1971-1975) and then vice chairman of the Department of Medicine at the University of Pittsburgh's medical school (1975-1979). Much of the correspondence is with colleagues in the medical profession regarding publications and conferences. There is also correspondence related to academic affairs at the medical school, and significant correspondence with University of Pittsburgh campus parking authorities about the difficulties of parking on campus.
- Photographs, 1948-1991; VII. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  The photographs in this series include group photographs of University of Pittsburgh's Medical School faculty, pictures of Shapiro teaching and in his office, and several professional portraits of Shapiro.